[{"answer": " Welcome back, Tanya.  How was your trip", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Oh, it was so great.  We had an amazing time", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Welcome back, Tanya.  How was your trip", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " What was your favorite part of the vacation", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Oh, it was so great.  We had an amazing time", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Well, you know, we were in France at the time of the World Cup", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 16, "question": " What was your favorite part of the vacation", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " The World Cup?  Whats that", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Well, you know, we were in France at the time of the World Cup", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": "Its the world champion tournament for soccer", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " The World Cup?  Whats that", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I knew that", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Its the world champion tournament for soccer", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, you know its not such a big deal here in the U.S. I didnt really know muc", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I knew that", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " What was it like", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well, you know its not such a big deal here in the U.S. I didnt really know muc", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Oh my god, the fans were so crazy.  It is a huge event over there", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 28, "question": " What was it like", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Did you go see any of the games", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Oh my god, the fans were so crazy.  It is a huge event over there", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " We didnt actually go to any of the games at the stadium, but we did go to a ba", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Did you go see any of the games", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " What was that like", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 34, "question": " We didnt actually go to any of the games at the stadium, but we did go to a ba", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " It was out of this world.  There were so many people packed in the bar t", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " What was that like", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": "Could you understand the rules of the game while you watched it", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 39, "question": " It was out of this world.  There were so many people packed in the bar t", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " I think I figured most of it out.  Each team had a bright jersey of a differen", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Could you understand the rules of the game while you watched it", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Which teams were playing in the game", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " I think I figured most of it out.  Each team had a bright jersey of a differen", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " We watched a few games, but the last one was the championship game of th", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Which teams were playing in the game", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Who won", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " We watched a few games, but the last one was the championship game of th", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " France did", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Who won", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " So you were in France when they won the World Cup", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " France did", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Yes.  It was such an unbelievable experience", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 52, "question": " So you were in France when they won the World Cup", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " I bet", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yes.  It was such an unbelievable experience", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " On TV, after they won, the team took off all of their cleats and threw them int", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 54, "question": " I bet", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " They must have been so happy", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 58, "question": " On TV, after they won, the team took off all of their cleats and threw them int", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Oh, they were.  The fans were even happier, I think.  Everyone in the bar jus", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " They must have been so happy", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " They must be huge soccer fans", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Oh, they were.  The fans were even happier, I think.  Everyone in the bar jus", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Definitely.  After the game was over, everyone moved outside to a celebratio", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " They must be huge soccer fans", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Definitely.  After the game was over, everyone moved outside to a celebratio", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " The streets were full of people.  No cars could even drive.  People wer", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Did you celebrate with them", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " The streets were full of people.  No cars could even drive.  People wer", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I had to.  Everyone was so happy and proud that I couldnt resist.  It was s", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Did you celebrate with them", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " I cant believe it", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I had to.  Everyone was so happy and proud that I couldnt resist.  It was s", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " We stayed out all night in the streets of Paris celebrating with everyone over th", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 81, "question": " I cant believe it", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Im so jealous.  I wish I could have been there", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " We stayed out all night in the streets of Paris celebrating with everyone over th", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " We would have had so much fun.  It was really an amazing time", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Im so jealous.  I wish I could have been there", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Ill have to start watching soccer more.  It sounds pretty exciting", "docId": "08-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " We would have had so much fun.  It was really an amazing time", "qSentId": 86}]
